中岛布兰登 6-1 3-6 10-7 门西克 · 赛后场上采访
Brandon, congratulations.
布兰登 恭喜你
What a roller coaster.
真是过山车
Great start and then things got a little tight
开局很好 后来打得有点紧
for you.
对你来说
Talk us through.
给我们讲讲
Yeah, I mean first match at Laver Cup,
是的 第一次打拉沃尔杯
obviously some nerves coming out,
肯定有点紧张
but you know,
不过你知道
it's pretty normal and eventually
这很正常 后来
when I lost the second set,
丢掉第二盘的时候
just try to tell myself to fight for every point.
就告诉自己每一分都要拼
You know, trust the guys on the bench,
相信板凳上的队友
trust myself, and, yeah,
相信自己 然后
really happy with the win.
赢了真的很开心
Nicely done.
打得漂亮
the guys on the bench.
板凳上的队友
Let's talk about that for you
我们就聊聊这个
because you don't get to play a lot
因为你平时很少
of team events and there are guys
打团体赛 而队里有人
that have been here
以前来过
before, but this is your debut.
但这是你的首秀
What's it like having that input?
听他们出主意是什么感觉？
Do you like that or not?
你喜欢还是不喜欢？
Yeah, I think it's great just to hear
我觉得很棒 能听听
their thoughts.
他们的想法
I mean, you know, of course,
我是说 当然了
they're all great tennis players,
他们都是很出色的球员
so very interesting to hear their thoughts
所以听他们怎么看很有意思
on the match, how I'm playing.
怎么看这场球 看我打得怎样
And it's also nice
而且也很好的是
to have some veterans out here that
队里有几位老将
that played Laver Cup a few times,
打过好几届拉沃尔杯
so definitely good to have all the guys
所以有全队在身边
on the team.
真的很好
What about we bring over the veteran
要不把老将请过来
and the legend in Andre Agassi?
传奇阿加西
Everybody, come on in.
大家都过来吧
Don't go. Brandon, now Andre,
别走 布兰登 现在问安德烈
at one point he goes up 3-0
有一阵他第一盘3比0领先
in the first set and he goes,
你当时想的是
I got nothing to say.
我没什么可说的
But then you had to try to do some work.
但后来你得干点活了
Well, no question about it.
没错 毫无疑问
I mean, listen,
我是说 听着
when you get off to a great start,
开局打得好的时候
there's no scoreboard pressure sort
球网两边
of on both sides of the net
都没有比分压力
and everybody's kind of free
大家都能放开
to do their thing.
打自己的
Second set, Mensik gets up early.
第二盘 门西克早早领先
They both, you know,
两个人 你知道
he's just started letting it fly,
他开始放开抡了
but then it quickly turns into a lot
但很快就变成了
of pressure.
满满的压力
And that's where I bet
这种时候我每次都
on this guy every time.
押这个家伙
I mean, he's rock solid.
他稳得像块石头
Welcome. You're initiated.
欢迎你 你正式入队了
And it was such an important point.
这一分太重要了
I mean, the first two matches of the day,
今天前两场
the first one could have gone your way,
第一场你们本来可能拿下
it doesn't.
结果没赢下来
And you have to absorb
你们得消化
that disappointment.
那份失望
No, no question about it.
没错 毫无疑问
I mean, you definitely want
你当然希望
to get off to a good start,
开个好头
but ultimately you're looking at this like
但归根结底你会这么看
if you know, some go their way,
有的归他们
some go our way.
有的归我们
We'll call it even. Intensity builds
就算扯平吧 越来越激烈
is one reason why this weekend's
这正是这个周末
so much fun.
这么好玩的原因
And what about as we go
那进入
into the evening session?
晚场呢？
You've got Alexander Bublik coming out.
你们派出的是布勃利克
So you got some different work to do.
你得做的功课就不一样了
Very different personality to Brandon.
和布兰登性格很不一样
You think?
你觉得呢？
I mean
我是说
this guy's like I'm not convinced he's real.
这家伙 我都不信他是真人
I think he's AI, you know?
我觉得他是AI 你知道吗？
He just goes about his business like point
他就是闷头打球
after point after point.
一分接一分
Bublik brings a lot of weapons to the table.
布勃利克手里武器很多
So let's hope
所以希望
that things fall our way again.
结果还能站在我们这边
But you know, you know, we're away,
不过 我们是客队
so I'm not going to say too much.
我就不多说了
You know, I'm just going
我就是
to go to work, too.
去干活
We are. Well done to you, Brandon.
我们是 布兰登 打得好
Andre, congratulations.
安德烈 恭喜